Welcome to Encrypted Signal Sharing Pool!
A privacy-preserving trading signal aggregation platform on Zama FHEVM.
Imagine multiple trading bots or participants
securely sharing and aggregating trading signals without revealing individual strategies.
Core values: Complete privacy protection using Fully Homomorphic Encryption (FHE).
Signals are encrypted on your device and remain encrypted throughout.
Intelligent aggregation from multiple signal sources for more accurate market predictions.
Fair revenue distribution based on contributions, incentivizing high-quality signals.
Real-time monitoring with a visual dashboard to track aggregated results and earnings.
Project advantages one: Industry-leading privacy.
End-to-end encryption, zero-knowledge computation—only final aggregated results are decrypted.
Individual signals stay encrypted forever; strategies are untraceable.
Advantages two: Real business scenarios.
Trading signal aggregation, decentralized signal markets,
privacy-protected quant trading, institutional data collaboration.
Advantages three: Technical innovations.
Dual-contract architecture: Mock version for quick testing, FHE version for production.
Gateway integration with timeout and retry mechanisms, progressive development.
Responsive design for desktop and mobile devices.
Zama tech stack: Fully leveraging the FHEVM ecosystem.
Core library @fhevm/solidity provides FHE encrypted types like euint32,
supporting homomorphic operations: addition, subtraction, multiplication, division on encrypted data.
Public decryption mechanism, Sepolia testnet configuration.
Applications: Store encrypted signals, perform mean or weighted average aggregations.
@fhevm/hardhat-plugin: Automatic contract compilation and network management.
@zama-fhe/relayer-sdk: Frontend encryption SDK—encrypt data in the browser,
generate proofs, upload only encrypted inputs.
Zama Gateway: Asynchronous decryption service with polling to avoid blocking.
Enterprise-grade reliability for decrypting aggregated results for user viewing.
Tech architecture advantages comparison:
Traditional schemes use plaintext storage and require decryption;
Our FHEVM offers end-to-end encryption, on-chain computation without trust, optimized performance.
System architecture: Frontend with React + Vite, including signal input, aggregation dashboard, revenue distribution.
Smart contracts: SignalPoolFHE.sol stores encrypted signals, performs FHE aggregation and revenue distribution.
Mock version for testing. Data flow: User input encrypted and uploaded,
FHE computes encrypted results, Gateway decrypts and updates state for frontend display.
Revenue distribution based on contributions, users withdraw earnings.
Quick start: Clone the project, install dependencies, configure env vars like contract addresses and RPC.
Run dev server to experience it.
Features: End-to-end encryption, homomorphic computation, selective decryption.
Aggregation algorithms: Mean, weighted average, signal voting.
Revenue mechanisms: Contribution tracking, automatic allocation, transparent and auditable.
User experience: Real-time monitoring, Echarts visualizations, responsive design.
Tech stack: Solidity 0.8.24, React 19.1, ethers.js, and more.
Use cases: Trading signal aggregation, quant strategy collaboration,
institutional data collaboration, decentralized signal markets.
Project highlights: Real business value, full technical implementation, excellent UX,
production-ready with error handling, comprehensive docs.
Contributions welcome! MIT license.
Visit Zama's site and FHEVM docs.
Built with ❤️ using Zama FHEVM.
Please refer to the user manual for details.
Thanks for watching!